

# CONTACT



051933053739



Luijhy9234@gmail.com



https://github.com/kailucho

# SKILLS

JavaScript

React Js

React native

Node Js

Redux

Graphal

Agile Methodologies

Scrum

**REST APIs** 

MySQL

WordPress

PHP

Flutter

AWS

нтмі

CSS

# LANGUAGES

SPANISH: native level

ENGLISH: advanced

### HOBBIES

Piano Skateboarding

# LUIJHY GUERRA

React | React Native Developer

Hello, I am a React programmer with more than 2 years of experience known for my ability to face new challenges. I feel trained in the JavaScript language and provide solutions to the challenges that arise, as well as good customer service to capture their needs.

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Systems Engineering and Computer Science 07-2019

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

Jan 2022 – Mar 2022 (3 mos)

LORO

Develop a mobile application with React native for the front and Backend Node JS, REST APIs, Express and MySql

#### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

Oct 2020 - Dec 2021 (1 year 3 months)

#### Gobierno Regional de Puno

Develop Web Applications with functionalities like budgets, reports, and statistical graphs, using Agile Methodologies in the process, with the following technologies. Front-End: React, Webpack, HTML, CSS, User Interface Design Responsive. Back-End: Node JS, Socket. io, REST APIs. DB: MySQL, Mongo DB.

#### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

Sep 2019 - Jul 2020 (11 months)

GrupoSistemas S.A.C.

Managed new functionalities for the hotel management system. Managed new functionalities for the touristic management system. Managed new functionalities facturation system of 5 companies. Technologies used were WordPress and Php, using the AWS S3 Flutter

#### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

Jan 2019 - Jul 2019 (7 months)

**SIGOBRAS** 

Develop Web Applications with functionalities like budgets, reports, and statistical graphs, using Agile Methodologies in the process, with the following technologies. Front-End: React, Webpack, HTML, CSS, User Interface Design Responsive. Back-End: Node JS, Socket. io, REST APIs. DB: MySQL, Mongo DB.